dealslist.com 2012-11-02

# 

This site is owned and operated by Infotitan, LLC. The material included herein, including site design, text, graphics, and the selection and arrangement thereof are copyrighted © by Infotitan, LLC. All Rights Reserved.  

Dealslist.com ([http://www.dealslist.com](http://www.dealslist.com/) and [http://www.dealofweek.com](http://www.dealofweek.com/)) is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement sets out our privacy policy and explains what we do with the personal information that we collect from our users. Please read the following to understand our views and practices regarding personal information, and how they pertain to you as you use our various features and services. This statement discloses the current privacy practices for our Web sites. If we make any substantive changes to this policy, we'll announce it on our site. 

We can be reached at [master@dealslist.com](mailto:master@dealslist.com)

For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible). We collect only the domain name, but not the e-mail address of visitors to our Web page, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations. The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes, not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes. 

With respect to cookies: We do not set any cookies. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address. We collect IP addresses for the purpose of system administration and for studying how our visitors use the site. With these information, we can further improve our service to you. 

When you click on links and/or ad banners that take you to third-party web sites, you will be subject to the third parties' privacy policies. While we support the protection of privacy on the Internet, Dealslist.com cannot be responsible for the actions of third parties. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement whenever interacting with any web site. 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.

Please note that Dealslist.com has financial relationships with some of the merchants mentioned here. Dealslist.com may be compensated if consumers choose to utilize the links located throughout the content on this site and generate sales for the said merchant.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the above address.
